humfans.com 2018-08-10

# Privacy Policy – HumFans

* * *

Lahmun is committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to the Website, including all visitors who access the Website or Service through any mobile application or other platform or device. Please read the following Privacy Policy which explains how Lahmun use and protect your information.

By visiting and/or using the Service on the Website, you agree and, where required, you consent to the collection, use, storage, disclosure and transfer of your information as set out in this policy.

#### 1\. INFORMATION THAT LAHMUN COLLECT FROM YOU

1.1. When you visit the Website or use the Service to make an Order from our Restaurant through the Website, you may be asked to provide information about yourself including your name, address, contact details (such as telephone and mobile numbers and e-mail address) and payment information (such as credit or debit card information). Lahmun may also collect information about your usage of the Website and Service and information about you from the materials (such as messages and reviews) you post to the Website and the e-mails or letters you send to us. Your telephone calls to us may also be recorded for training and quality purposes.

1.2. By accessing the Website or Service using mobile digital routes such as (but not limited to) mobile, tablet or other devices/technology including mobile applications, then you should expect that our data collection and usage as set out in this Privacy Policy will apply in that context too. Lahmun may collect technical information from your mobile device or your use of the Website or the Service through a mobile device, for example, location data and certain characteristics of, and performance data about, your device, carrier/operating system including device and connection type, IP address, mobile payment methods, interaction with other retail technology such as use of NFC Tags, QR Codes or use of mobile vouchers. Unless you have elected to remain anonymous through your device and/or platform settings, this information may be collected and used by us automatically if you use the Website or Service through your mobile device(s) via any our mobile application, through your mobile’s browser or otherwise.

#### 2\. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

2.1. Your information will enable us to provide you with access to the relevant parts of the Website and to supply the Service. It will also enable us to bill you and enable us to contact you where necessary concerning the Service. For example, Lahmun may use your information to provide you with status updates or other information regarding your Order by e-mail, telephone, mobile or mobile messaging (e.g. SMS, MMS etc.). Lahmun will also use and analyse the information Lahmun collect so that Lahmun can administer, support, improve and develop our business, for any other purpose whether statistical or analytical and to help us prevent fraud. Where appropriate, now and in the future you may have the ability to express your preferences around the use of your data as set out in this Privacy Policy and this may be exercised though your chosen method of using the Service, for example mobile, mobile applications or any representation of the Website.

2.2. Lahmun may use your information to contact you for your views on the Service and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the Website or the Service.

2.3. Where you have indicated accordingly by giving your consent, you agree that Lahmun may use your information to let you know about our other products and services that may be of interest to you including services that may be the subject of direct marketing and Lahmun may contact you to do so by post, telephone, mobile messaging (e.g. SMS, MMS etc.) as well as by e-mail.

2.4. Where you have indicated accordingly by giving your consent, you agree that Lahmun may also share information with third parties (including those in the food, drink, leisure, marketing and advertising sectors) to use your information in order to let you know about goods and services which may be of interest to you (by post, telephone, mobile messaging (e.g. SMS, MMS etc.) and/or e-mail). Lahmun may also disclose your information to help us analyse the information which Lahmun collect so that Lahmun can administer, support, improve and develop our business and services to you. For example, by providing anonymised personal information to Google Analytics – see attached link – “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps”, (located at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners).

2.5. You agree that Lahmun may disclose personal information which Lahmun collect from you to other companies that also hold information about you. Lahmun may also collect personal information from those other companies. Lahmun and/or those companies may combine the information in order to better understand your preferences and interests, thereby enabling them and us to serve you better.

2.6 If you do not want us to use your data in this way or change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know by using the contact details set out in paragraph 8 below, by amending your profile accordingly or by using the opt-out facilities provided (eg an unsubscribe link).

2.7. Please note that by submitting Reviews regarding the Website, Service, you consent to us to use such Reviews on the Website and in any marketing or advertising materials. Lahmun will only identify you for this purpose by your first name and the city in which you reside (and any other information that you may from time to time consent to us disclosing).

#### 3\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

3.1. The information you provide to us will be transferred to and stored on our servers which may be in or outside India, and may be accessed by or given to our staff working outside India and third parties who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes notified to you from time to time in this policy.

3.2. The third parties with whom Lahmun share your information may undertake various activities such as processing credit card payments and providing support services for us. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Lahmun will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

3.3. If our business enters into a joint venture with, purchases or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed or transferred to the target company, our new business partners or owners or their advisors.

3.4. Lahmun may use the information that you provide to us if Lahmun are under a duty to disclose or share your information in order to comply with (and/or where Lahmun believe Lahmun are under a duty to comply with) any legal obligation; or in order to enforce the Website Terms and any other agreement; or to protect our rights or other third parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and other organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and prevention.

#### 4\. SECURITY AND DATA RETENTION

4.1. Lahmun take steps to protect your information from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure and against misuse, interference, loss, destruction and damage. Once your information is no longer required for any purpose for which it may be used or disclosed by us, and Lahmun are not required by law to retain the information, Lahmun will destroy the information or ensure that it is de-identified.

4.2. Where you have registered an account with us and chosen a password which allows you to access certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Lahmun advise you not to share your password with anyone. Unless Lahmun negligently disclose your password to a third party, Lahmun will not be liable for any unauthorised transactions entered into using your name and password.

4.3. All user details captured by us are stored securely at all times and will never be provided to any unauthorised third parties. All credit card details are protected using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. Credit card details are handled by leading PCI compliant providers of secure credit card processing solutions. Lahmun will never save your actual credit card details. Lahmun may simply save a reference to your card, which is called a token. This token is provided to us by the payment provider. Saving the token means that for future credit card transactions Lahmun can give you the option to charge the same card you used previously without having to re-enter the card details.

4.4. However, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although Lahmun will take reasonable steps to protect your information and make sure it is safe and secure and Lahmun use a number of physical, administrative, personnel and technical measures to protect your personal information, Lahmun cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website; any transmission is at your own risk. For the avoidance of doubt, Lahmun will not in any circumstances be liable to you, or third parties, for loss or damage arising from credit card fraud or identity theft.

#### 5\. COOKIES

5.1 Lahmun may collect personal information about you when you use and access our website. While Lahmun do not use browsing information to identify you personally, Lahmun may record certain information about your use of our website, such as which pages you visit, the time and date of your visit and the internet protocol address assigned to your computer.

Lahmun may also use ‘cookies’ or other similar tracking technologies on our website that help us track your website usage and remember your preferences. Cookies are small files that store information on your computer, TV, mobile phone or other device. They enable the entity that put the cookie on your device to recognise you across different websites, services, devices and/or browsing sessions. You can disable cookies through your internet browser but our websites may not work as intended for you if you do so.

Lahmun may also use cookies to enable us to collect data that may include personal information. For example, where a cookie is linked to your account, it will be considered personal information. Lahmun will handle any personal information collected by cookies in the same way that Lahmun handle all other personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### 6\. ACCESSING AND UPDATING

6.1. You have the right to see the information Lahmun hold about you and to ask us to make any changes to ensure that it is accurate and up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us using the contact details set out in paragraph 8 below.

#### 7\. Changes to our Privacy Policy

7.1. Lahmun reserves the right to alter all or any part of this Privacy Policy. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted to the Website and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification. Lahmun encourage you to check our website periodically to ensure that you are aware of our current Privacy Policy.

#### 8\. Other Websites

8.1. Our Website may have links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to the Website. You should therefore read the privacy policies of the other websites when you are using those sites.

#### 9\. CONTACT

9.1. All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed. Lahmun will acknowledge your complaint and respond to you regarding your complaint within a reasonable period of time. If you think that Lahmun have failed to resolve the complaint satisfactorily, Lahmun will provide you with information about the further steps you can take. All correspondence should be [cc@lahmun.com](mailto:cc@lahmun.com)
